Take a good look, all of you.
The General's Manor of Northern Jin has committed treason.
The spy, Li Zhi'an,
is the culprit behind your ruined families.
Li Zhi'an,
I'll graciously let you die knowing the truth.
Traitor! Traitor!
You national turncoat!
Traitor to the nation!
Traitor! Traitor! Traitor!
Kill this traitor!
Kill this national turncoat!
Your General's Manor of Northern Jin,
has long been a hollow shell due to treason.
On the day of your wedding,
everyone in your General's Manor, including your father and mother, was slaughtered.
Impossible!
How could the Li family commit treason?
I don’t believe it!
Where is Zhu Huaichen?
Bring him here to see me!
Li Zhi'an.
It's a pity that you're blind.
Otherwise, I would love for you to see with your own eyes.
How Huai Chen killed your parents,
taking their lives one stab at a time.
I don't believe it.
I want Zhu Huaichen to tell me personally.
Release him.
Do you really think the person who married you is Zhu Huaichen?
If it weren't for the Li family's Longyu treasure,
he wouldn't have kept you around this long.
Li Zhi'an.
Today, I'll send you on your final journey.
In your next life, don't be such a blind and foolish person again.
Kill that traitor!
Kill!
Zhi'an!
Zhu Huaichen, why?
No, I'm Zhu Huaijin.
Zhi An
Zhi An, Zhi An
Where is this place?
Am I... am I still alive?
Have I regained my sight?
Isn't this the day of my wedding?
How did I come back here?
Why are there bloodstains?
Could it be that my parents have already...
No!
On the day of your wedding,
your parents and everyone in the General's Manor were slaughtered.
My wedding day turned out to be the day my entire family was massacred.
And the person I married wasn’t Zhu Huaichen...
Then who was it?
Zhu Huaichen...
You were even ashamed to put your name on the marriage contract.
So be it. This way, we are cleanly severed.
Heaven has given me a second chance at life.
This time...
I will personally avenge my family.